Guide to the Lucy Monroe Calhoun Family Photographs and Papers, 1886-1993 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 RL.11103
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Developing out paper and gelatin silver photographs, 1900-1941 and undated; 1
  - Outside Beijing, 1900-1939; 3
    - Temple of Quetzalcoatl stairs, 1930s; 3.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 19, Print RL11103-P-452)
      Temple of Quetzalcoatl
    - Four men on a platform at the Temple of Quetzalcoatl, 1930s; 5.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 19, Print RL11103-P-453)
      四人站在墨西哥羽蛇神庙
    - William J. Calhoun reading, 1910s; 4.25 x 6.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-454)
      威廉·嘉乐恒在看书
      WJC
    - William J. Calhoun? and unidentified woman on porch, reading, 1900s; 6.25 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-455)
      威廉·嘉乐恒和一位妇女在屋后凉亭里看书
    - William J. Calhoun, reading on summer porch, 1910s; 4.75 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-456)
      威廉·嘉乐恒夏日里在凉亭看书
    - William J. Calhoun, seated in wicker chair, 1910s; 5.5 x 7.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-457)
      威廉·嘉乐恒坐在藤椅上
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun, seated portrait, 1910s; 7 x 9 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-458)
      露西·嘉乐恒坐着
      Lucy Monroe Calhoun.
      Studio--Moffett
    - Unidentified woman and child with boat on Lucy Calhoun's porch in Illinois, 1910s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-459. 1)
      伊利诺伊州露西·嘉乐恒家中，一位妇女和一个手拿帆船模型的小孩
      On porch at Aunt Lucy's on Eric Street.
    - Unidentified woman and child with boat on Lucy Calhoun's porch in Illinois, 1910s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 20, Print RL11103-P-459. 2)
      At Aunt Lucy's (397 Eric Street)
      Version of RL11103-P-459. 1.
    - Wu Tai Shan. Pines at Pi San Ssu (Bishan Temple), 1930s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-493)
      五台山碧山寺内松树和石碑
    - Palos Park, Ill, 1909; 13.25 x 10.25 in. (Box 3, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-521)
      伊利诺伊州Palos Park
      257-9-25-1909 Palos Park. One of the first Prairie Club
    - Incense burner, Tanzhe Temple., 1920s; 2 x 2 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Slide-box RL11103-SL-001)
      北京西山潭柘寺香炉
      Tan Che Szu LMC#20
  - Unidentified location, 1920-1929; 4
    - Garden, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-004)
      花园
    - Kites for sale in market, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-005)
      卖风筝的摊子
    - Courtyard with stone centerpiece, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 23, Image RL11103-N-006)
      院子和中间的石座
      Negative of RL11103-P-581.
    - A private graveyard, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-460)
      陵墓
      A private graveyard
    - Two men stand on bridge to unidentified building, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-461)
      两人站在房前
    - Unidentified town by waterway, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-462)
      小镇上的塔和房屋
    - Animal feeding from bowl, 1920s; 2.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-463)
      吃食的小动物
    - Gate and windows in wall, 1920s; 4 x 2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-464)
      门外看花园，围墙上的花窗
    - Terrace and steps to unidentified building, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-465)
      高大的殿堂和堂前石阶
    - Detail of post, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-466)
      石柱上的盘龙
      Detail of post.
    - aquamarine Kwan Yin (Guanyin) statue, 1920s; 3 x 4 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-467)
      观音塑像
      aquamarine Kwan Yin--Ann Carrère
    - First pilau, in pinkish white marble, 1910s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-468)
      石牌坊
      First pilau--end arch. pinkish white marble
    - Unidentified man with Lucy Monroe Calhoun, 1920s; 5 x 3.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-469)
      露西·门罗·嘉乐恒和一名男子站在庭院里
    - Pilau, among trees, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-470)
      树荫里的石牌楼
    - Gate with public sign, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-471)
      城门楼上的"仁丹"广告
    - Stairs to incense burner, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-472)
      大殿前的铜香炉
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun [?] holding a ball for a dog, 1920s; 2.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-474)
      院中露西·门罗·嘉乐恒和小狗玩球
    - Women seated on a boat. Lucy Monroe Calhoun, 2nd from right?, 1920s; 4.5 x 2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-475.1)
      船上的四位外国女子，右边第二位是露西·门罗·嘉乐恒？
    - Women seated on a boat. Lucy Monroe Calhoun, 2nd from right?, 1920s; 4.5 x 2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-475.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-475.1.
    - Two women sitting on a wall beneath an arch, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-476)
      两名女子坐在矮墙上
      [Scot]man or Acolman, Mexico
    - One man and two women standing beneath a double-arched gate, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-477.1)
      三人站在拱门旁
      [no known title] or Acolman, Mexico
    - One man and two women standing beneath a double-arched gate, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-477.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-477.1.
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun and Polly Root Collier seated on a wall beside an incense burner, 1920s; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-478.1)
      露西·门罗·嘉乐恒和波莉·鲁特·科利尔坐在大香炉旁的矮墙上
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun and Polly Root Collier seated on a wall beside an incense burner, 1920s; 3.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-478.2)
      Aunt Lucy and Polly
      Version of RL11103-P-478.1.
    - Gate in Walter Kirk's garden, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-479)
      沃尔特·柯克家花园中的拱门
      Gate in Walter Kirk's garden
    - Three men walking in a Chinese temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-480)
      寺庙里的人群
    - Road, with low-walled bridge, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-481)
      小路，路上的矮桥
    - Altar with statue inside a metal lotus flower, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-482)
      莲花宝座中的佛像
    - Lama beside a pillar, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-483)
      喇嘛站在廊柱旁
    - Men outside Chinese shop, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-484)
      街边商铺门前的人们
    - Unidentified fortress gate, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-485)
      残破的要塞门
    - Terrace, with pole, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-486)
      院落中的杆子
    - Altar with statue in armor, draped in a cloth, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-487)
      佛像，祭坛
    - Allan Priest & his #1 boy Lao [Sum], 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-488)
      普爱伦和他的大弟子老孙
      Allan Priest & his #1 boy Lao [Sum]
    - Allan Priest, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-489)
      普爱伦
      Allan Priest
    - Altar with stone statue, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-490)
      祭坛上的石佛像
    - Carved altar with cloth-draped Buddah and servant statues, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-491.1)
      宝座上的菩萨和身旁的侍者
    - Carved altar with cloth-draped Buddah and servant statues, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-491.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-491.1.
    - Carved altar with cloth-draped Buddah and servant statues, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-491.3)
    - Courtyard with round gate, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-492)
      院落，拱门
    - Brick wall with gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-495)
      院墙和院门
    - Head of broken statue, 1920s; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-496)
      断裂下来的佛头
    - Line of camels near a gate, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-497)
      驼队准备过城门
    - Group of Chinese men outside a building beside a pole, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-498)
      院子柱子旁的一群人
    - Chinese military troops in formation, with flag, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-499)
      一群中国士兵举旗列队在铁路旁
    - Eight Chinese military troop members, in a row, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-500)
      八名中国士兵并排站立
    - Wooden wagon pulled by oxen, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-501)
      牛车
    - Woman standing beneath decorative arch, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-505)
      妇女站在石拱门前
    - Baskets in a merchant's stall, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-506)
      卖篮框的店铺
    - Series of gates before the Imperial Vault of Heaven, Temple of Heaven, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-507)
      天坛皇穹宇前石牌坊
    - Stone Chinese lion, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-508)
      石狮子
    - Stairway to dagoba, the Black Temple, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-509)
      黑寺佛塔
    - Two cauldrons beside a staircase, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-510)
      石阶两旁的两个大铜缸
    - Boats and ships off the mainland, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-511)
      船只
    - Ships in South China Sea?, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-512)
      南海（？）上的船只
    - Detail of Chinese boat, with family, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-513)
      船上一家人
    - The ship Goeben, starboard side, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-514)
      戈本号舰船右舷
    - The ship Goeben, port side, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-515)
      戈本号舰船左舷
    - Street scene with detail of building's roof, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-516)
      街道旁的建筑
    - Detail of marble bridge, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-517)
      大理石桥近拍
    - Chinese man walking on a pier, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-518)
      码头上站立的男子
    - Detail of stone dragon staircase, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 21, Print RL11103-P-519)
      石桥上的雕龙
    - Steles and unidentified buildings, 1920s; 9.75 x 7.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 22, Print RL11103-P-520)
      大殿和石碑
      Photograph backed with silk.
  - Beijing riots, 1912; 5
    - The Rami barricade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-522)
      街道上的路障
      No. 2. A closer view of the Rami barricade shown in No. !
    - A battalion of 500 men of the 15th U.S. Infantry arrive in the compound of the American legation, in Peking, on the morning of March 3d. for the further protection of the legation. These troops came from Tientsin and have just marched into the Legation compound when this picture was taken, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-523)
      1912年3月3号早上，美国第15步兵营的500个士兵到达使馆驻地保护公使馆。部队从天津过来，这张照片是他们刚到达时拍摄的。
      No. 3 A battalion of 500 men of the 15th U.S. Infantry arrive in the compound of the American legation, in Peking, on the morning of March 3d. for the further protection of the legation. These troops came from Tientsin and have just marched into the Legation compound when this picture was taken.
    - A mountain battery--guns on mules--attached to 15th U.S. Infantry, arriving in American Legation compound, with the battalion of infantry, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-524)
      骡车上的大炮，随美国第15步兵营到达使馆驻地。
      No. 4 A mountain battery--guns on mules--attached to 15th U.S. Infantry, arriving in American Legation compound, with the battalion of infantry
    - Quartermaster's wagon of the 15th U.S. Infantry arriving in American compound Peking--Showing entrance gate to the compound in the foreground, and officer's quarters of the U.S. Marine guard on the left, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-525)
      美国第15步兵营的军需部份到达使馆驻地，左边是使馆驻地大门，右边是海军陆战队官员
      No. 5 Quartermaster's wagon of the 15th U.S. Infantry arriving in American compound Peking--Showing entrance gate to the compound in the foreground, and officer's quarters of the U.S. Marine guard on the left.
    - Col. Arrowsmith, commanding the 15th U.S. Infantry, reporting his arrival with his battalion of troops, to the American minister, 1912; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-526)
      阿罗史密斯上校带领15步兵营向公使报告
      No. 6 Col. Arrowsmith, commanding the 15th U.S. Infantry, reporting his arrival with his battalion of troops, to the American minister.
    - Colonel Arrowsmith telling the American minister some of the incidents of his trip up from Tientsin, 1912; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-527)
      阿罗史密斯上校向公使报告从天津到这里一路上发生的情况
      No. 7 Colonel Arrowsmith telling the American minister some of the incidents of his trip up from Tientsin.
    - The foreign troops which were hurried to Peking at the time of the riots-Feby 29th -March 2nd, 1912, paraded and marched through the streets of the city, to make a demonstration of force and thereby to over awe the rioters. A squad of American marines--mounted on Chinese ponies--headed this column. In this picture they are standing by their horses waiting for the order to mount, 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-528)
      1912年3月2号各路外国军队到达北京，他们列队在街上巡逻，威吓参加兵变的军队。一队美国海军陆战队士兵站在马旁，等待命令准备上马。
      No. 9 (No Number 8) The foreign troops which were hurried to Peking at the time of the riots-Feby 29th -March 2nd, 1912, paraded and marched through the streets of the city, to make a demonstration of force and thereby to over awe the rioters. A squad of American marines--mounted on Chinese ponies--headed this column. In this picture they are standing by their horses waiting for the order to mount.
    - Mounted squads of Germans, Italians, and Russians--forming for the parade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-529)
      骑兵队的德国、意大利和俄国士兵们整装待发
      No. 10 Mounted squads of German, Italians, and Russians--forming for the parade
    - German troops marching up to take their place in the parade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-530)
      德国军队步行参加巡街
      No. 11. German troops marching up to take their place in the parade.
    - The Dutch (Holland) marines in the line of parade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-531)
      巡街队伍中的荷兰军队
      No. 13. The Ductch [sic.] (Holland) marines in the line of parade.
    - The parade starts--Germans head the column--Note the crowd of natives--on the left--who are really friendly to the demonstration because the presence of the foreign troops means peace for the city., 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-532)
      巡街开始，德国军队领头，左边街边站着的中国老百姓对巡街很欢迎，因为外国军队的到来会给城里带来安定
      No. 12 The parade starts--Germans head the column--Note the crowd of natives--on the left--who are really friendly to the demonstration because the presence of the foreign troops means peace for the city.
    - The French contingent marching in the parade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-533)
      巡街队伍中的法国军队
      No. 14 The French contingent marching in the parade
    - The British troops in the parade, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-534)
      巡街队伍中的英国军队
      No. 15. The British troops in the parade.
    - A column of American marines in the parade. Don't they look good!, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-535)
      巡街队伍中的美国军队，他们多棒！
      No. 16. A column of American marines in the parade. Don't they look good!
    - The entrance to the "Forbidden City" Picture taken from the top of the Chien Men, 1912; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 24, Print RL11103-P-536)
      紫禁城大门，照片从前门上拍摄
      No. 17 The entrance to the "Forbidden City" Picture taken from the top of the Chien Men. [Crossed out: Tartar Wall}
  - Presentation photographs Chinese box one, 1920-1939; 6
    - Lucy's dogs beside the marble lion in the courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-537)
      [no known title.]
      Copy of RL11103-P-027.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Chrysanthemums in the main courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-538)
      Version of RL11103-P-018.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Bedroom., 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-539)
      Version of RL11103-P-065.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Duke Tsai Tze's garden in Peking, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-540)
      北京贝子载泽的花园
      Garden at Duke Tsai Tze's
      Peking. Duke Tsai Tze's garden
    - The 9th Panchen Lama in the Ying T'ai (Ying Tai), Nan Hai, 1925; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-541)
      第九世班禅喇嘛在南海瀛台
      Peking. The Panchan Lama in the Ying T'ai--Nan Hai
    - Water garden at Nan Hai, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-542)
      南海中的水边花园
      Peking. Nan Hai
    - Nan Hai path, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-543)
      南海花园小径
    - Hatamen Street, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-544)
      哈德门（崇文门）大街
      Peking. Hatamen Street
    - Entrance to Coal Hill Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-545)
      景山寿皇殿
      Peking. Coal Hill Temple
    - Alex Kirk's Peking garden, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-546)
      D[rum?} Tower house of Alex Kirk
      Peking. Garden near the D[rum?] Tower (Alex Kirk)
    - The Great Wall, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-547)
      Chang Cheng
    - The Great Wall from the air, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-548)
      空中俯瞰长城
      The Great Wall from the air
      Peking to Kulgan. The Great Wall from the air.
    - Wu Tai Shan. Pines at Pi San Ssu (Bishan Temple), 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-549)
      山西五台山，碧山寺
      Wu T'ai Shan, Pi Sau Szu
      Shansi. Wu Tai Shan. Pines at Pi San Ssu.
      Copy of RL11103-P-493. Photograph has black border.
    - Wu Tai Shan. White jade Kuan yin at Pei Shan Ssu (BishanSi), 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-550)
      山西五台山，碧山寺白玉观音像
      Shaun si. Wu T'ai shan. Pei Shan Szu. White jad kuan yin.
      Shansi. Wu T'ai Shan. White jade Kuan yin at Pei Shan Ssu.
      Version of RL11103-P-400. Photograph has black border.
    - The route to Hsi Yu Szu (Xiyu Si or Yunju Temple), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-551)
      通向西域寺(云居寺)的路
      to Hsi Yu Szu
      Trip with Henry Moncal & Mayo Newhall. The route to Hsi Yu Szu.
    - Span of Marco Polo bridge, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-552)
      Lu Ko Chiao. Marco Polo bridge
    - Marco Polo bridge, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-553)
      卢沟桥头的华表
      Lu Ko Chiao. Marco Polo br.
      Version of RL11103-P-162. Photograph has black border.
    - Pavilion at Marco Polo bridge, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-554)
      Lu Ko Chiao. Pavilion at Marco Polo bridge
    - Cemetery of Confucius Memorial Pailou at Qufu, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-555)
      曲阜，孔林，万古长春坊
      Chu fu P'ai-lou
      Chufu. Confucius Memorial Pailou
    - Gateway to the Tomb of Confucius, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-556)
      曲阜，孔林，孔子墓道
      Chu fu Entre to tomb
      Chufu. Gateway to the Tomb of Confucius.
    - South China near Shao-hsing, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-557)
      中国南方绍兴附近
      Shao-[ching?] [illegible]
      South China near Shao-hsing
    - Qufu. The Tomb of Confucius, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-558)
      Chufu. tomb
      Chufu. The Tomb of Confucius
      Version of RL11103-P-242. Photograph has black border.
    - T'ai Shan (Tai Shan), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-559)
      泰山
      T'ai Shan
    - T'ai Shan (Tai Shan) gate, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-560)
      泰山山门
    - Hsi Ling. Western Qing Tombs., 1920s (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-561)
      清西陵
      Hsi Ling
      Hsi Ling. Western Tombs.
    - Detail of robed statue on altar., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-562)
      北京西山潭柘寺佛像
      Tan Che Szu
      Tan Che Ssu (Tanze Temple)
    - Right side of living room at Lucy's house, with flowering plants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-563)
      Version of RL11103-p-040.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Living room looking toward gallery, with large plant on the coffee table, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 4, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-564)
      Version of RL11103-p-045.1. Photograph has black border.
  - Presentation photographs Chinese box two, 1910-1939; 7
    - Right side of living room, with Anna seated on arm of chair, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-565)
      会客室右面，安娜坐在椅子扶手上
      Anna
    - Lucy Monroe Calhoun, 3/4 length portrait, 1920s; 7 x 9 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-566)
      露西·门罗·嘉乐恒
      Lucy Monroe Calhoun
    - William J. Calhoun, 3/4 length portrait, 1910s; 6.25 x 8.25 (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-567)
      威廉·嘉乐恒
      Wm. J. Calhoun, Boissonnas & Caponier, 12 Rue de la Paix, Paris
      Boissonnas & Caponier, 12 Rue de la Paix, Paris
    - Nankow pass, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-568)
      南口关
      Nou? Kou pass
      Peking & Kaligan, Nankow Pass
    - Tatung, Yungang caves, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-569)
      大同，云冈石窟
      Ta-t'ung, Yung Kan caves
      Tatung, Yung Kan caves
    - Lucy's? bedroom, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-570)
      Version of RL11103-P-058.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Fa Hai-Ssu fresco; photograph by Serge Vargassoff, 1920s; 7.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-571)
      法海寺壁画，模式口村附近，斯尔格·沃特加索夫拍摄
      Copyright Serge Vargassoff
      Fresco, Fa Hai-Ssu. Near Mo-shih Kow village, Peking, Serge Vargassoff, Peking #1898
    - Xiantong Temple pagodas, Wutai Mountians, 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-572)
      Wu T'ai Shan, Hsien tung szu
      Shansi, Wu T'ai Shan, Golden pagodas at Haien Tring Ssu
      Copy of RL11103-P-284.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Two statues on altar, close up, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-573)
      北京西山潭柘寺观音塑像近景
    - Temple of Heaven gates, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-574)
      天坛，圜丘，石牌坊
      T'ien-tan
      T'ien t'an
    - Two men with camel train, Kalgan (Zhangjiakou), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-575)
      两人带着驼队，喀拉干(张家口)
      Kalgan
    - Throne in the Palace of Heavenly Purity, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-576)
      the Forbidden City Throne Room
      Version of RL11103-P-117. Photograph has black border.
    - Musical Instruments at the Emperor's wedding, 1921; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-577)
      溥仪大婚时的乐器
      Emperor's wed[d]ing
      Peking. The Forbidden City. Musical Instruments at the Emperor's wedding
    - Blue Temple, Peking, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-578)
      天坛，北京
      Blue temple
      Peking. Blue Temple
    - Jehol. Hsien-kung, Xumi Fushou Temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-579)
      承德，须弥福寿之庙寺门，石象
      Je ho. Hsien (Hsin?) kang
      Jehol. Hsien-kung
    - Garden at Daruanfu Hutung, in snow, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-580)
      大阮府胡同花园雪景
      Garden at Ta Juan Fu Hutung
    - Garden at Daruanfu Hutung, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-581)
      大阮府胡同花园中间的石座
      Peking. Garden at Ta Juan Fu Hutung
    - Rock garden at Daruanfu Hutung, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 9, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-582)
      大阮府胡同花园中的奇石园
      Peking. Garden at Ta Ruan Fu Hutung